Guide to the Faculty Senate records, 1937-2008 RG0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Faculty Senate records
1937-2008
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0003
14 Linear Feet
The Faculty Senate of The George Washington University was formed in 1961. Materials in this collection include meeting minutes, agendas, photographs, memos, reports, and activites files.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1, 3, and 5 are closed to research for 50 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Faculty Senate.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Faculty Senate of The George Washington University was formed in 1961. It evolved out of the faculty ferment of the 1950's coupled with a discontent over lack of faculty participation in University governance. The activities of the American Association of University Professors (AAUP) chapter organized by Professor of History Wood Gray, along with concern about the eminent retirement of then President Cloyd Heck Marvin and concern for his replacement, also drove the move to create a body which could have a say in the way the University was run. With the encouragement of Dean of Faculties Oswald S. Colclough, a committee was formed Sept. 17, 1958 to study the problem of University government, although this was not stated in the resolution adopted.
The resolution, drafted by Professor of English Fred Tupper, read "that the University faculty create a Committee to study the policies of the University with the object of recommending to the appropriate University officials procedures best calculated to bring about the advancement of the University's academic programs." Professor of History Roderic Davison outlined the development of the Faculty Organization Plan which embodied the Faculty Assembly and the Faculty Senate. This plan was passed by the Board of Trustees in 1960 and the first meeting of the Senate took place Jan. 13, 1961. Its greatest task was the revision of the Code of Ordinances for the Faculty.
Over the years, the Faculty Senate has worked for a major medical insurance plan, free tuition for the children of faculty, and improvements to the University Library. In the 1960's GW's Faculty Code and Ordinances served as a national model through the AAUP and by 1970 some 300-400 campuses had adopted similar plans. The various committees of the Senate continue to address concerns such as admissions, appointments, salaries, promotions, budget, libraries, physical facilities, and academic freedom. The Senate is under the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs.
The Faculty Senate publishes the Faculty Code.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include meeting minutes, agendas, photographs, memos, reports, and activites files. They range in date from 1937-2004, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Secretaries of the Faculty Senate.
Collection Organization
Arrangement cannot be determined.
Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Policies and institutions; Washington (D.C.); Employees; Photographs; American Association of University Professors; George Washington University
- Office records, 1961-1988; RG0003 Series 1; 6 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 4, Box 2, Box 3)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes information on meeting minutes, joint committee of faculty and students, physical facilities, athletics, Maury Hall incident, student life, correspondence, faculty code and organization plan, etc., 1961-88.
  Formerly ACC#90
  - Administrative Matters, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Matters, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Appointment, Salary and Promotion Policies, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Appointment, Salary and Promotion Policies, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Appointment, Salary and Promotion Policies, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Appointment, Salary and Promotion Policies, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Athletics, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Athletics (missing files for 1968 - 1974), 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Educational and Admissions Policies, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Educational and Admissions Policies, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Senate Committee on Educational Policy Questionnaire on Modified Semester and Long Intersession Circulated with memorandum from Chairman Reuben E. Wood to Members of the Faculties (on campus), 12/16/1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Educational and Admissions Policies, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Educational and Admissions Policies, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fiscal Planning and Budgeting, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fiscal Planning and Budgeting, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Honors and Academic Convocations, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Libraries Committee, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Physical Facilities, 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Physical Facilities, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Physical Facilities, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Professional Ethics and Academic Freedom, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Professional Ethics and Academic Freedom, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Professional Ethics and Academic Freedom, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Professional Ethics and Academic Freedom, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Research Committee, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - University and Urban Affairs, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - University Development and Resources, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - University Development and Resources, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Public Ceremonies Committee, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Student Financial Aid Committee, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Senate Physical Facilities reel-to-reel taped minutes, 12/10/1971-02/08/1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - GWU Faculty Organization Plan, 1965-1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - GWU Faculty Code, 1945-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Drugs Policy, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Coffeehouse (Hill), 09/1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Committee on the Performing Arts, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Committee to Student Career Services Office, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Task Force Report, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Commencement, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Special Committee on Health Care Benefits, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dr. Phelps' Report on Intercollegiate Athletics, an update, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Student Relationships Committee, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Student Relationships Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Student Council, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - President Elliott's Misc. Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Evaluation Report of GWU from Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 02/12/1967-02/15/1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Committee on the Judicial System, 1971-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Committee on the Judicial System, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Insurance Carrier Report (Starrs), 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Division of Experimental Programs, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cooperative Agreements with Universities/NASA, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Black Student Union and Disadvantaged Students, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Misc. from Student Organizations, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Campus Security, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - College of General Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Coordinating Committee for the Poor People's Campaign and Workshop, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Correspondence re Campus Disturbances, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - formerly Residence Hall Court, 1975-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - formerly Student Court, 1967-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - GWU Patent Policy, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - All-University Assembly Proposal, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - The Bilsky Report on Men's Athletics, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Lyndale George Report on Women's Athletics, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee Faculty Club Organization, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Maury Hall Incident, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Productivity Questionnaires, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Student Life Survey, 10/1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Equal Opportunity Program (Administrative), 1969-1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Comission for the Year 2000 (Report), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Special Senate Meeting on the Report of the Commission for the Year 2000, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Summary of Faculty Questionnaire on Report of the Commission for Year 2000, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Senate Survey Report on Report of the Commission for the Year 2000, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Building 13 Advisory Council, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Title 34 - Rules and Regulations of DC Regarding Employment, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Tuition Exchange Program, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - SVAC - Student Volunteer Action Committee (Abolished 1981), 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Thor Opinion, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Handicapped Student Services, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Student/Faculty Committee on Appeals (abolished in 1988), 1968-1986 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Presidential Appeals Board (abolished 1988), 1972-1987 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Yeshiva University, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Special Committee on Retirement, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - President's Ad Hoc Committee on Retirement, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - University Planning Process, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Minutes, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Minutes, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Minutes-A, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Minutes-B, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Minutes, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Minutes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Minutes, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Minutes-A, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Minutes-B, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Minutes, agendas, records, 1956-2008; RG0003 Series 2; 5 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes faculty senate minutes, agendas, and committee records, they range in date from 1956-present.
  Formerly ACC#105
  - Faculty Senate--resolutions--index, 1961-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate--special committee on Conflict of Interest, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees-general, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees-administrative matters committee (as they affect the faculty), undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees-admissions & advanced standing, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--annual report, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--appointment, salary, and promotion policies, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees-athletics committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees-educational policy committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--executive committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--fiscal planning & budgeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--physical facilities, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--professional ethics & academic freedom, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees-resources and development, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--public ceremonies, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees-scholarship, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--university objectives, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Senate--standing committees--university resources, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Senate, 1956-1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 10/1967-01/1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 02/1968-05/1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 10/1969-02/1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 03/1970-06/1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1970-11/1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 12/1970-03/1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1971-01/1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 02/1972-05/1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 04/1972-05/1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1972-01/1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 02/1973-08/1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1973-01/1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 02/1974-05/1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1974-01/1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 02/1975-05/1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1975-01/1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 02/1976-06/1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1976-02/1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 03/1977-12/1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1979-12/1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1980-05/1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 08/1980-12/1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1981-05/1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 08/1981-04/1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 12/1985-05/1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 03/1987-01/1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 03/1988-10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 11/1988-04/1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/1989-12/1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1990-05/1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1990-01/1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/1991-12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1992-08/1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1992-05/1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 02/1993-03/1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 04/1994-12/1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1995-04/1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 08/1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 08/1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/1995-12/1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1996-04/1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/1996-12/1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1997-04/1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/1997-12/1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1998-08/1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1998-12/1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/1999-08/1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/1999-12/1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/2000-05/2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 08/2000-10/2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/2001-04/2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/2001-12/2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/2002-04/2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/2002-08/2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/2002-12/2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/2003-03/2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 04/2003-05/2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/2003-10/2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 11/2003-03/2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 04/2004-12/2004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 01/2005-03/2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 04/2005-05/2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 10/2005-11/2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 11/2005-02/2006 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 03/2006-05/2006 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 05/2006-09/2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 09/2006-11/2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate--minutes & agenda, 12/2006-01/2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes and Agendas, 02/2007-05/2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes and Agendas, 08/2007-12/2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes and Agendas, 01/2008-03/2008 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes and Agendas, 04/2008-05/2008 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes and Agendas, 09/2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Committee files, 1968-1980; RG0003 Series 3; .5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes information on committees on athletics and university & urban affairs files, 1968-80.
  Formerly ACC#120
  - Sentate Committee on Urban Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committee on University & Urban Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Educational Opportunity Program, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Committee on University & Urban Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Committee on University & Urban Affairs, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on University & Urban Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee on University & Urban Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate Committee on Athletics, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate Committee on Athletics, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Photographs, Faculty Senate Sessions, 1986-2003; RG0003 Series 4; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes photographs of faculty senate sessions, academic years 1986-2001, 2002/03.
  Formerly ACC#1023
  This series has a container list in electronic form, please ask staff for assistance.
- Office records, 1975-1997; RG0003 Series 5
  This series contains faculty senate activities files. They range in date from 1975-97.
  Formerly ACC#1027
- Records, 1937-2004; RG0003 Series 6; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains correspondence, memorandums, reports, brochures, questionnaires, forms, agendas, meeting minutes, resolutions, amendments, regulations, procedures, and policies. They range in date from 1937 to 2004. They concern the Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, academic dishonesty, establishment of the Joint Committee of the University Senate and the Student Assemble, the All University Assembly, nominations to the Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, release of student information, discrimination, recognition of student organizations, stipends, health advisory committee, Office of University Ombudsman, annual reports of the Joint Committee of the University, publications, honors, awards, the articles of the Student Assemble, communication with students, student rights, the George Washington Award, the Faculty Organization Plan, and the Faculty Code.
  Formerly vertical files
  - Awards & Prizes--George Washington Award, 1976-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Code, 1937-1960, 1937-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Code, 1961-1980, 1964-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Code, 1981-2004, 1986-2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Organization Plan, 1960-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Organization Plan Booklets, 1965-Present, 1965-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate, 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Joint Committee Of Faculty & Students, 1970-1971, 1970-04/16/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Joint Committee Of Faculty & Students, 1971-72, 05/25/1971-02/05/1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Joint Committee Of Faculty & Students, 1973, 11/01/1972-12/14/1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Joint Committee Of Faculty & Students, 1973-74, 05/15/1969-05/13/1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Joint Committee Of Faculty & Students, 1974, 12/01/1969-10/11/1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)